Finding Aid to the Women's Project Theater records SSC.MS.00361
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. Administrative Files, 1972-2010; 29.042 linear feet (34 containers)
  - Directors, Timothy Near, 1992 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Deborah Nitzberg, 1991-1998 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Amy Ober, 1980 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Elizabeth Williams Omilani, 1984 (Box 61)
  - Directors, M. Elizabeth Osborn, 1981-1993 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Sharon Ott, 1991 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Tom Palumbo, 1992-1998 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Annie-B Parson, 2000 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Caymichael Patten, 1975-1989 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Rebecca Patterson, 2000 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Diane Paulus, 1999 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Livia Perez, 1979-1980 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Carey Perloff, 1982-2003 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Lisa Peterson, 1989-2003 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Victoria Pero, 1998-2002 (Box 61)
  - Directors, David Petrarca, 1989 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Renee Philippi, 1997-2001 (Box 61)
  - Directors, June Plager, 1978-1979 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Lynn Polan, 1981-1986 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Joanne Pottlitzer, 1986-1991 (Box 61)
  - Directors, June Pysacek, 1998-2003 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Jean Randich, 1982-1993 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Tim Raphael, 1990 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Amy Redford, 1999-2002 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Alyson Reed, 1997 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Elinor Renfield, 1976-1992 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Nancy Rhodes, 1982-1993 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Joumana Rizk, 1993-1994 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Mary Robinson, 1990-2002 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Carol Rocamora, 1993 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Gaby Rodgers, 1973-2001 (Box 61)
  - Directors, June Rovenger, 1981-1985 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Barbara Rosoff, 1979-1981 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Victoria Rue, 1978-1979 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Eva Saks, 1998-1999 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Amy Saltz, 1979-1987 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Nancy Salomon (Box 61)
  - Directors, Kirsten Sanderson, 1988-1994 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Eleny Scotes, 2000 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Serret Scott, 1989-1999 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Bartlett Sher, 1998 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Betsy Shevey, 1978-1990 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Dorothy Silver, 1979-1988 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Joan Micklin Silver, 1981-1992 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Ethan Silverman, 1990 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Jim Simpson (Box 61)
  - Directors, Elyse Singer, 1994-2002 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Roberta Sklar, 1983 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Carolyn Jackson Smith (Box 61)
  - Directors, Elaine Smith, 1991-1994 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Beverly Smith-Dawson, 1992 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Florence Stanley, 1984-1988 (Box 61)
  - Directors, June Stein, 1985 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Alison Summers, 1991-1999 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Melanie Sutherland, 1996-2002 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Carol Tanzman, 1982-1994 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Beatrice Terry, 2001-2002 (Box 61)
  - Directors, John Tillinger, 1999 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Virlana Tkacz, 1990 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Susana Tubert, 1989-2000 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Ching Valdes-Aran, 1995-1999 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Valeria Vasilevski, 1980-1997 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Irving Vincent, 1988-1990 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Jean Wagner, 1992-1994 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Paul Walker (Box 61)
  - Directors, Emma Walton, 1991 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Claudia Weill, 1983 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Adrienne Weiss, 1994 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Iona Weissberg, 1992-1994 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Melanie White, 1998 (Box 61)
  - Directors, B.J. Whiting, 1980-1986 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Maurya Wickstrom, 1990-1993 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Rachel Wineberg, 1993-1994 (Box 61)
  - Directors, Frank Wittow, 1994 (Box 62)
  - Directors, Evan Yionoulis, 1989-2000 (Box 62)
  - Directors, Allison Eve Zell, 2000-2002 (Box 62)
  - Director's Forum, 1989-1996 (Box 62)
  - Video recording of Director's Forum Workshop of the Women's Project, 1983; 2 items (Two VHS cassette tapes) (Box 97)
  - Sound recordings of The Directors Workshop, 1984-1989; 11 items (11 audiocassettes) (Box 95)
  - Video recording of Director's Workshop for Real Thing discussion, 1984; 1 items (One VHS cassette tape) (Box 97)
  - Directory of Directors, 1999-2000 (Box 62)
  - Eleni Screening, 1985-1986 (Box 62)
  - Festival of One Act Plays, 1983-1984 (Box 62)
  - Financial, Annual Reports, 1987 (Box 62)
  - Financial, Budgets, 1987-1993 (Box 62)
  - Financial, Contributions, 1988 (Box 62)
  - Financial, Income and Expenses, 1985-1988 (Box 62)
  - Financial, Notes, 1988 (Box 62)
  - Financial, Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 62)
  - Financial, Voided Receipts, 1988 (Box 62)
  - Ford Foundation, 1981-1989 (Box 62, Box 63)
  - Fundraising, Appeals, 1991-1993 (Box 63)
  - Fundraising, Rejections, 1984-1985 (Box 63)
  - Fundraising, Reports, 1985-1988 (Box 63)
  - Fundraising, General, 1980-1989 (Box 63)
  - Girls Just Wanna Have Fund$, 2007 (Box 63)
  - History of the Women's Project, 1971-1987 (Box 63)
  - Iowa Center for the Arts Broadcast, 1992; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 95)
  - In No Man's Land Workshop, 1993-1994 (Box 63)
  - International Festival New York, 1985-1991 (Box 63, Box 64)
  - Jerome Foundation, 1984 (Box 64)
  - Journal, 1984-2003 (Box 64)
  - The Journey program, 1970-1999 (Box 64)
  - Lisa's Theater-going, 1999-2001 (Box 64)
  - Lifetime, 1994-1995 (Box 64)
  - Lorca Women's Project, 1986-1987 (Box 64)
  - Lorine Niedecker: The "Solidatry Plover", 1970-1989 (Box 64)
  - Mailers, 1984-1985 (Box 64)
  - Makin' Whoopi Event, 1980 (Box 64)
  - Mapping Theatrical Territories Festival, 1986-1988 (Box 64, Box 65)
    The Mapping Theatrical Territories Festival was WP Theatre's contribution to the 1988 New York International Festival. WP Theatre put on Letters to a Daughter from Prsion and If You Strike the Woman, You Strike the Rock. For the latter play, the theater partnered with the Vusisizwe Players, from Soth Africa. Materials include playbills, scripts, correspondence, scrapbooks, photos, and administrative files.
  - Massachusetts Cultural Council, 1996-1998 (Box 65)
  - Member Lists, 1996 (Box 65)
  - Memorabilia, 2004 (Box 65)
  - Move to New Theater, 1996 (Box 65)
  - National Endowment of the Arts Grant, 1990 (Box 65)
  - Next Wave Festival, 1987-1992 (Box 65)
  - Newsletter "Dialogues", 1985-1997 (Box 65)
  - No Victims, Some Humor Series, 1997 (Box 65)
  - One Acts, 2002-2003 (Box 66)
  - Out of Their Minds, 1984-1985 (Box 66)
  - Photographs, 1951-2004 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, General, 1998-2001 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Joyce Aaron, 1980-1989 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Catherine Allen, 1999-2000 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Michele Aldin, 2002 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Lynn Alvarez, 1979-1996 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Carolyn Anderson, 1988-1991 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Eliza Anderson, 1990-1991 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Jane Anderson, 1987 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Valetta Anderson, 1991-1999 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Shelley Berc, 1982-1988 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Brooke Berman, 2000-2001 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Randee Berman, 1993 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Kathleen Betsko, 1980-1981 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, June Bingham, 2001-2003 (Box 66)
  - Playwrights, Sallie Bingham, 1967-2003 (Box 66, Box 67)
  - Sound recording of Sallie Bingham, 1990; 1 items (One audiocassette) (Box 96)
  - Playwrights, Patricia Bosworth, 1978-2002 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Ariane Brandt, 1997 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Deborah Broovort, 2001-2003 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Carole Braveman, 1993-1996 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Kate Browne, 1993-2001 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Susan Brownmiller, 1990-1995 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Suzanne Bradbeer, 2001-2002 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Cindy Bullens, 2001 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, France Burke, 1978-1984 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Sophie Burnham, 1978-1986 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Johann Carlo, 1984 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Marina Carr, 1999 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Jo Carson, 1989-1992 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Rosemarie Caruso, 1985-1993 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Claire Chafee, 1994-2002 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Marisha Chamberlain, 1990-1991 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Laura Maria Censabella, 1980-1995 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Kitty Chen, 1989-2003 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Miyagawa Chiori, 1999 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Paula Cizmar, 1982-2000 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Martie Evans Charles, 1978-1994 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Pearl Cleage, 1992-2002 (Box 67)
  - Playwrights, Darrah Cloud, 1988-2000 (Box 67, Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Patricia Cobey, 1983-1998 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Alice Eve Cohen, 1984-1994 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Carolyn Cole, 1987-1988 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Kathleen Collins, 1980-2002 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Constance Congdon, 1987-2002 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Cindy Cooper, 1986-1996 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Kia Corthorn, 1993-2001 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Clare Coss, 1986-2001 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Cyndi Coyne, 2003 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Bette Craig, 2000 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Migdalia Cruz, 1988-1994 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Gretchen Cryer, 1989-1993 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Juni Dahr, 1993 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Cheryl Davis, 2000-2001 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Elsa Davis, 2001 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Lisa D'Amour, 2000-2002 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Sarah Daniels, 1998 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Christina De Lancie, 2000 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Mindi Dickstein, 2000 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Elizabeth Diggs, 1986-1987 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Nancy Donohue, 1984 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Marjorie Duffield, 1992-1995 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Susan Dworkin, 1992-2001 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Joan Eades, 1985-1986 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Susan Egloff, 1990-1992 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Barbara Blumenthal Erhlich, 1996 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Eve Ensler, 1988-2001 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Annie Evans, 1995-1996 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Linda Faigao-Hall, 1997-1998 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Nancy Fairstone, 1991 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Kitty Felde, 2000 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Barbara Field, 1992-1994 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Catherine Filloux, 1991-2002 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Alex Finlayson, 1986-1990 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Susan Flakes, 1983-1997 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Joan Floyd, 1992 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Daisy Foote, 1990-1994 (Box 68)
  - Playwrights, Maria Irene Fornes, 1985-2003 (Box 68, Box 69)
  - Sound recordings of Maria Irene Fornes Workshop, 1985-1999; 7 items (7 audiocassettes) (Box 95)
  - Playwrights, Juliana Francis, 1996-1999 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Cynthia Gates Fujikawa, 1993-1995 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Donna Gabel, 1986-1987 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Mary Gallagher, 1986-1990 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Gail Galloway, 1983-1993 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Griselda Gambara, 1991-1992 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Amparo Garcia, 1996-1997 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Nancy Garrett, 1979-1986 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Judy GeBauer, 1993-1994 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Paula Giddings, 1990-1991 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Daphne Gil, 1996 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Julie Gilbert, 2000 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Judith Gilhousen, 1980-1982 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Penelope Gilliant, 1980-1992 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Rebecca Gilman, 1999-2001 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Leslie Glass, 1981-1983 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Jessica Goldberg, 2000 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Rose Leiman Goldemberg, 1977-2002 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Gloria Goldsmith, 1979-1980 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Dana Leslie Goldstein, 1996-1997 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Patricia Goldstone, 1987 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Jill Gorham, 1987 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Ezzat Goushegir, 1992-1993 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Roma Greth, 1979-1990 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Nancy Grome, 1987-1995 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Denise Hamilton, 1986 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Elizabeth Hansen, 1997 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Leslie Harrell, 1987-1998 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Karen Hartman, 1998-2003 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Laura Harrington, 1985-2002 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Deanna Harris, 1983 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Molly Haskell, 1993-1998 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Nancy Hasty, 2000 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Robyn Hatcher, 1989-1993 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Julie Hebert, 1996-2002 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Mary Hebert, 1994 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Paula Heil, 1993-1996 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Carol Hemingway, 1983-1987 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Jane Stanton Hitchcock, 1981-1989 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Pat Holley, 1996-1999 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Katherine Houghton, 1984-2000 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Velina Hasu Houston, 1989-2001 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Holly Hughes, 1990-1992 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Lisa Humbertson, 1992-1994 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Margaret Hunt, 1993-1994 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Momoko Iko, 1979-1980 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Corinne Jacker, 1996 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Elaine Jackson, 1983 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Julie Jensen, 1984-2003 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Cindy Johnson, 2000 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Michael Johnson, 1989-2001 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Elinor Jones, 1999 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, June Jordan, 1984-1988 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Diane Kagan, 1979-2002 (Box 69)
  - Playwrights, Marcy Kahan, 1997-1999 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Susan Kander, 1987-1994 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, C. Michele Kaplan, 2002 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Pat Kaufman, 1984-1992 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Kerry Kennedy, 1987 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, E. Katherine Kerr, 2001 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Alice Knox, 1988 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Carson Kreitzer, 1997-2002 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Gail Kriegel, 1982-2002 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Pamela Blafer Lack, 1984 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Jenny Laird, 2001 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Christina De Lancle, 1999 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Shirley Lauro, 1976-2003 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Barbara Lebow, 1991-1994 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Bokara Legendre, 1995-2001 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Cherylene Lee, 1993-1995 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Stephanie Lehmann, 1998 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Gen LeRoy, 1991-1994 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Patricia Lin, 2001 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Jessica Litwak, 1989-2002 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Kate Long, 1988-1994 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Rosa Lowinger, 1991-1993 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Nancy Lubet, 1993-1994 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Patty Lynch, 1979-1993 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Susan Lukas, 1978-1980 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Anne Lux, 1985 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Ann-Marie MacDonald, 1991 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Sharman Macdonald, 1989-1992 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Wendy MacLeod, 1990-1999 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Carol Mack, 1977-1994 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Ann Magnuson, 1988-2001 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Emily Mann, 1982-2003 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Melanie Marnich, 2000 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Jill Maynard, 1986 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Ivey McCray, 1984-1990 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Elizabeth McDonald, 1996-1997 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Heather McDonald, 1988-2002 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Julie McKee, 2001-2002 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Karen Meadows, 1986-1994 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Cassandra Medley, 1979-2002 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Lois Meredith, 1989-1994 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Kim Merrill, 2001 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Eve Merrium, 1985 (Box 70)
  - Playwrights, Marlene Meyer, 1992-2003 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Pam Mills, 1992-1996 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Lysse Miller (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Michele Miller, 2002 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Chiori Miyagawa, 1991-2002 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Monika Monika, 1998 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Honor Moore, 1978-1981 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Lavonne Mueller, 1984-2002 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Brighde Mullins, 1997-2002 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Meredith Muncy, 1990-1991 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Suzen Murakoshi, 1997 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Phyllis Nagy, 1979-1998 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Gloria Naylor, 2001 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Renfreu de St Lurence Neff, 1986 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Janet Neipris, 1980-2000 (Box 71)
  - Playwrights, Juliette McGinnis Nelson, 1998 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Sally Nemeth, 1987-1994 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Diane Ney, 1990-1994 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Gail Noppe-Brandon, 1993-1998 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Joyce Carol Oates, 1991-2002 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Kira Obolensky (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Edna O'Brien, 1988 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Sally Ordway, 1979-1988 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Elaine Oslo, 1983-1987 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Elizabeth Page, 1983-1990 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Suzan-Lori Parks, 1989-2002 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Debbie Patrick, 1990 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Sybille Pearson, 1978-1999 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Peggy Pettitt, 1991 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Mary Bracken Phillips (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Leigh Podgorski, 1988 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Regina Porter, 1993-1994 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Emily Prager, 1991-1994 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Mary Sue Price, 1989-1994 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Rebecca Pritchard, 1997-1998 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Phyllis Purscell, 1981-2202 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Laura Quinn, 1991-1992 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Bonnie Lee Moss Rattner, 2001 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Theresa Rebeck, 1997-2000 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, M. Kilburg Reedy, 1985 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Elizabeth Scales Rheinfrank, 1999-2002 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Kate Robin, 2000 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Carmen Rivera, 1997-2003 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Hillary Rollins, 2002 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Joan Rosenfels, 1996 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Sharon Houck Ross, 1992-2001 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Cheryl Royce, 1997-1999 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Enid Rudd, 1977 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Sarah Ruhl, 2002 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Cate Ryan, 1992-2002 (Box 72)
  - Playwrights, Kate Moira Ryan, 1992-2003 (Box 72, Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Beth Schatcher, 1993 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Joan Schenkar, 1982-2002 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Barbara Schneider, 1982 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Sarah Schulman, 2002 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Edele Edling Shank, 1980-1981 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Nina Shengold, 1984-1985 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Lionel Shriver, 1982 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Gail Sheehy, 1990-2002 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Sarah Levine Simon, 2000 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Patty Gideon Sloan, 1979-1980 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Anna Deavere Smith, 1984-2001 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Anna Deavere Smith, 1982-1990 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Elaine Smith, 1992 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Kat Smith, 1986-1987 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Lois Smith, 1987-1991 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Beverly Smith-Dawson, 1993 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Diana Son, 1993-2001 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Joan Ross Sorkin, 1999 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, J.S. Staniloff, 1999 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Shelagh Stephenson, 2002 (Box 73)
  - Sound recording of Frances Stenhager[?], playwright?, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 95)
  - Playwrights, Lydia Stryk, 1993-2003 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Lynda Sturner, 1998 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Dolores Sutton, 1995 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Caridad Svich, 1989-2002 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Elizabeth Swain, 2000 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Maura Swanson, 1982 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Deborah Swisher, 2000 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Luna Tarlo, 1980-1988 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Judy Tate, 1999 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Regina Taylor, 1991-2001 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Nadja Tesich, 1978-1990 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Janet Thomas, 1986 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Kristine Thatcher, 1988-1991 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Joan Vail Thorne, 1979-2002 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Tracy Thorne, 1997 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Sharon Tipsword, 1978-1980 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Kathleen Tolan, 1982-2001 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Sandra Torres, 1991 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Luisa Valenzuela, 1980-1994 (Box 73)
  - Playwrights, Dorothy Valesco, 1978-1994 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Judith Viorst, 1992 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Paula Vogel, 1982-2002 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Naomi Wallace, 1993-2003 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Lucy Wang, 1994-2002 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Ara Watson, 1986 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Penny Weiner, 1991 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Gina Wendkos, 1984-2001 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Dolores Whiskeyman, 2000 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Carol Williams, 1985 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Sheri Wilner, 1995-2002 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Bridgette Wimberley, 2000-2001 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Deborah Grace Winer, 1995-2000 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Valerie Windsor, 1993 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Elizabeth Wong, 1992-1993 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Maryrose Wood, 1997 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Sue Woolfe, 1994-1998 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights, Eliza Wyatt, 2001 (Box 74)
  - Playwrights Lab, 1996-2002 (Box 74)
  - Playwright's Manual: Surviving New York, 1985 (Box 74)
  - Playwriting Competition, 1988 (Box 74)
  - Sound recording of Pointed Views Sessions I-3, 10 items (10 audiocassettes) (Box 96)
  - Press Clippings, 1978-1990 (Box 74)
  - Publications, 1985-1993 (Box 74)
  - Publications, Statistical Reports, 1987-2002 (Box 74)
  - Publications, Women Artist's Statistics, 1995-2001 (Box 75)
  - Publications, plays from the Women's Project, 1980 (Box 75)
  - Publications, Women directing in theater, 1980 (Box 75)
  - Publicity, 1978-1994 (Box 75)
  - Publicity, Village Voice - 'Signs of Life', 'Letters Home', 1985-1986 (Box 75)
  - Publicity, 1978-1994 (Box 75)
  - Publicity, posters and artwork, 1989; undated (Box 98)
  - Recommendations, 1982-1998 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsal Schedule, 1979-1985 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - ticket statistic reports, 1983-1984 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - final report/statistics, 1985-1986 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - rehearsal schedules, 1985-1986 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings, Statistical Report, 1985-1986 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings Program, 1983-1984 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings, 1984-1985 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - WP press releases and schedule listings, 1982-1985 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - workshop publicity, 1987-1995 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - list, 1978-1979 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings, 1978-1987 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - Acrobatics, 1979-1980 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - financial reports, 1980-1981 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - press, 1978-1981 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - Jeffrey Richards and Associates Press releases, 1979-1981 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - WP press releases, reading schedules, authors, director bios, narrative publicity packs, 1979-1981 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - lists of readings, 1979-1983 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - invitations to these readings, 1980-1981 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings -cast list, 1982 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings -cast list, 1982-1988 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - listings, 1983-1984 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - listings, 1983-1985 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - listings, 1985-1986 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings -mailers/flyers, 1985-1986 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - listings, 1985-1986 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - listings, 1986-1987 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - production preludes, 1987 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - directors, 1987-1988 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings, 1987-1988 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - revision of RR for WP Journal, 1988 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - contracts, 1988-1989 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - series, 1988-1989 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - cast lists, 1988-1996 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings - spring programs, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings -programs, 1989-1990 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings, 1989-1990 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings -contracts, 1989-1990 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings -contracts, 1990-1991 (Box 75)
  - Rehearsed Readings, 1990-1991 (Box 75)